Wyatt Sell

515 McFaddin Hall, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 339-1403

wyattsetonsell@gmail.com

wyattsell.com | github.com/wyatt | linkedin.com/in/wyattsell/

Computer Engineer with extensive experience in software development, both individually and in large teams. Proficient in all stages of product creation, including branding, UI design, testing architectures, deployment, etc.

Currently studying for a Masters in Electrical and Computer Engineering.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SAMARITAN SCOUT | Volunteering Search Engine

Remote

Software Engineer

May 2024-Present

- Engineered ETL workflows to scrape, interpret and ingest large quantities of data using LLMs.
- Created end-to-end authentication, search and flagging functionality in Supabase, Typescript and React. Managed and maintained infrastructure platforms.
- Redesigned and created onboarding and login flows, search user interface and functionality (filtering, etc.) as well as account pages, and various additional pages.

REMNOTE, INC. | Memory-oriented Note Taking app

Remote

Software Engineer

January 2022–June 2023

- Delivered multiple features for a complex note taking and knowledge management platform, including PDF annotation, improved text formatting, app-wide dark mode and many others.
- Collaborated asynchronously with 12+ developers, contributed to feature proposals, engaged in code review and led team bonding activities
- Led efforts to improve development experience and reduce regressions, through producing style guidelines, tests and utilities. Refactored and simplified large components.

CORNELL UNIVERSITY

Ithaca, NY

Computer Science Consultant

January-May 2024

- Co-teach 15+ students key computer science paradigms and help them to develop robust, clear code
- Advise students on assignments, run regular office hours to clarify conceptual misunderstandings
- Grade exams and assignments, offering personalised feedback and advice

EDUCATION

CORNELL UNIVERSITY

Ithaca, NY

Masters of Engineering in Electrical and Computer Engineering, Minoring in Comparative Literature August 2023-Present

PROJECTS

REVISIO

www.revisio.app

Founder and Sole Creator

April 2021-Present

In the UK, intense studying for exams forms a key cornerstone of our education, and results in unhealthy stress and anxiety for thousands of students. Being a student myself, and failing to find a tool that adequately met my needs in terms of study planning and online resource consolidation, I decided to build it myself. I learnt about databases, user authentication, hosting, web scraping, payment processing, data parsing, algorithms and dozens of things in between.

- Spaced repetition algorithms schedule when is best for a student to revise, run nightly as a separate microservice and manipulate the database efficiently.
- Study resources can be shared and added within the UI by users, where they can be approved by an administrator. Web scraping automates adding resources by parsing, caching and uploading from a variety of study websites.
- Users can compete and interact in a leaderboard system against friends
- Users can create and publish their own courses in a shared environment where other users can add them to their own account.
- Credits act as a form of currency which can be earned by referring other users and sharing resources, or eliminated altogether by purchasing a paid plan.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Proficient in Typescript (NodeJS, Svelte, React, NextJS) and Python
- Experience with Postgres, Redis, Git, Docker, Storybook, Figma, HTML & CSS